transitions.com 2008-05-15

# Transitions.com - Privacy

At Transitions Optical, Inc., user privacy is of utmost concern. We are committed to your privacy and security, and to providing you with the best possible user experience.

What do we mean by privacy? We will never disclose your personally identifiable information without your consent - repeat - we will not sell, trade, loan or otherwise make available your personal or contact information to anyone - EVER - unless you give us specific permission.

Here's how we collect and use information from you in our efforts to provide the highest quality user experience:

 **IP Address** \- Your IP or "Internet Protocol" address and other site usage data is used to gather broad demographic information. This data helps us serve you better by telling us how visitors use our Web site.

 **Cookies** \- Our site uses "cookies," small files stored by your browser, to help keep track of site visits. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information, nor do we share them with anyone. We use cookies to track user trends and improve the areas of our site that our users find valuable.

 **Registration** \- We use customer contact information from registration forms to send you information related to our products and services if you consent to receiving such mailings. We use your email address as a unique identifier in our record system to verify communications from you, and to send you newsletters and promotion offerings that you ask to receive or to tell you about changes to the Transitions Optical, Inc. Web site.

 **Your Security** \- Transitions Optical, Inc. has taken the following important measures to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. First, we store no financial information or social security information on our site. Second, we encrypt all personal information transmitted to or from our site using 40-bit SSL (secure socket layer) strong encryption using a VeriSign Digital Certificate. 

**Outside Links** \- While on the Transitions Optical, Inc. site, you may be led to other Web sites. Be aware that other sites may collect data and personal information and operate according to their own privacy practices. Please remember that, once outside of our site, any information you submit is outside of our control.

 **Contacting Us** \- If at any time you feel that the Transitions Optical, Inc. Web site has not adhered to this policy, email us at [customerservice@transitions.com](mailto:customerservice@transitions.com) and we'll do our best to determine any problem and quickly respond. If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at [customerservice@Transitions.com](mailto:customerservice@transitions.com).

 **Revisions to this Policy.** Transitions Optical, Inc. reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on this site.

Experience Transitions lenses

Transitions lenses help optimize your sight in every light as they quickly lighten or darken depending on the amount of UV rays present. 

Visit the Transitions Web site for  
your local region.
